top10homeremedies.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Top 10 Home Remedies

The owners of [www.top10homeremedies.com](https://www.top10homeremedies.com/) follow a very strict privacy policy. As a reputed home remedy site, we cater to the needs of the users and hence give high importance to the privacy policy.

Here are some of the basic segments of our privacy policy:

 **What type of information do we collect?**

For simply browsing the website, we do not need any kind of information from your end. However, we need to collect certain basic information from you when you register on our website, respond to a poll or fill out a form. The type of information that you may need to provide are:

  * Name
  * Age
  * Email address
  * Gender
  * Nationality

 **Why do we need your information?**

All or some of the basic information provided by you may be used in one of the following ways by us:

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our website
  * To establish customer relationship
  * To maintain responsible customer relation
  * To care to special needs of users
  * To process transactions
  * To manage the operations of this site
  * To meet legal requirements

 **Note:** No information provided by you, whether public or private, will be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

 **How do we protect your information?**

No matter, whether you are using our site for submitting a request or simply browsing the web pages of our website, we guarantee your personal privacy information is safe with us. To give full protection to valuable information offered by you online, we have designed our website in such a manner that there can be no loose ends in safeguarding your privacy.

The security statement is designed after thorough research and regular updates are done to ensure full protection of personal information. Highly sophisticated security processes and technologies are used to ensure protection from unauthorized access and improper use of information provided by the users.

As we value the personal information of a user, we have come up with a safe and secure environment. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

All the databases of our website are accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. The aim and objective of this security system is to create a high level of consumer trust and confidence while using this website.

 **Do we use cookies?**

To enhance your online experience we use cookies. Cookies are small files that are transferred by the website from the hard disk of the user’s computer. These files provide a piece of personal information about you or your preferences.  We also use third party advertisements on [www. top10homeremedies.com](https://www.top10homeremedies.com/) to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google. [www. top10homeremedies.com](https://www.top10homeremedies.com/) uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of [www. top10homeremedies.com](https://www.top10homeremedies.com/) and user behavior concerning ads, products and the services we offer.  
You may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en).

 **Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or transfer any of the information provided by you to outside parties.  Information can be disclosed to trusted third parties who help in conducting our business, but it is done so only when those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

 **What about third party links used in our website?  **

Occasionally, at our website, we may use links of other websites. These third party links are provided solely to provide more information on topics that may be useful to the users. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies.  When you go to another website from our website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Hence, we have no responsibility or liability for the content provided by these third party websites.

 **Is there any kind of age screening?**

We operate this website in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Hence, we do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. This requirement is clearly posted during the registration process. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

If we become aware that we have inadvertently received information from a registered user under the age of thirteen, we will delete the information from our records as soon as we get to know about it.

 **How can you access and update your information?**

We allow our users to review, correct or change the information provided by them during the registration process. Users may change information at any time and as often as necessary. If you face any kind of problems while updating your information, you can contact us using the e-mail address at the bottom of this page.

 **Will there be any changes to this Privacy Policy?**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time with or without notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page only.

 **NOTE:** By using the site, [www.top10homeremedies.com](https://www.top10homeremedies.com/), you agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. You should access our privacy policy regularly to ensure you understand our current policies.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using this email address – info  @   top10homeremedies.com
